So I'm up early filling orders for my store, Amanda Land Exports.
I have my show, Views for Amanda Land, in a couple hours.
And I'm here watching the Hulu documentary on Katrina.
And among the many feelings that it's given me, it actually gave me clarity as to why I get so offended at people who suggest that I'm not black.
Not about, you know, folks who consider themselves FBA and Ados who tried to suggest that I am not black American.
I got so, I get so offended.
And I was watching this and I realized why I get so offended.
Because who are these people that tell me who's not my people?
I'm like six minutes into this and I'm already riled up.
It's not even 7 a.m.
And the amount of emotions that are, that are, of emotions that are filtering through me are because I am deeply connected.
And I will remain deeply connected.
And I wish more of us were deeply connected to each other and to understanding who our people are.
And by the way, your people don't even need to be your people because you're the same ethnicity.
They can be your people because y'all have the same heart.
You know, y'all have the same empathy.
And you don't have to Rachel Dolezal it to feel for those people.
Because Palestinians are my people.
Whether I am Muslim, Arab, Palestinian or not.
Your people are the people you feel for.
In addition to the people that live within you.
I'll see y'all at 10 a.m. Eastern at YouTube Amanda Seals TV.